At the frontlines of life, near the end of
innocence, came the beginning of manhood.
A Midnight Clear is a drama, war, history film directed by Keith Gordon.
In 1944 France, an American Intelligence Squad locates a German Platoon wishing
to surrender rather than die in Germany's final war offensive.
The two groups of men, isolated from the war at present, put aside their differences and spend Christmas
together before the surrender plan turns bad and both sides are forced to fight the other.
Bud Miller, played by Peter Berg.
Mel Avakian, played by Kevin Dillon.
Stan Shutzer, played by Arye Gross.
Will Knott, played by Ethan Hawke.
Vance 'Mother' Wilkins, played by Gary Sinise.
Paul 'Father' Mundy, played by Frank Whaley.
A Midnight Clear is a 1992 American war drama film written and directed by Keith Gordon, and starring an
ensemble cast that features Ethan Hawke, Gary Sinise, Peter Berg, Kevin Dillon, and Arye Gross.
It is based on the novel by William Wharton.
Set toward the end of World War II, the film tells the story of an American
intelligence unit that finds a German platoon that wishes to surrender.
The film explores themes of germany, world war ii, christmas.
The tone is emotional.